[
  {
    "userId": "player1",
    "currentPuzzle": {
    "puzzleId": "w2",
    "type": "Word-Riddle",
    "prompt": "What has keys but can’t open locks?",
    "answer": "Keyboard",
    "description": "A riddle puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  },
    "totalScore": 150,
    "completedPuzzles": [
  {
    "puzzleId": "w1",
    "type": "Word-Cipher",
    "prompt": "Unscramble the letters: CSEAPE",
    "answer": "ESCAPE",
    "description": "A simple word scramble puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  },
  {
    "puzzleId": "w2",
    "type": "Word-Riddle",
    "prompt": "What has keys but can’t open locks?",
    "answer": "Keyboard",
    "description": "A riddle puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  },
  {
    "puzzleId": "w3",
    "type": "Word-Anagram",
    "prompt": "Unscramble the letters: SILENT",
    "answer": "LISTEN",
    "description": "An anagram puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  }
],
    "toDoPuzzles": [
  {
    "puzzleId": "w1",
    "type": "Word-Cipher",
    "prompt": "Unscramble the letters: CSEAPE",
    "answer": "ESCAPE",
    "description": "A simple word scramble puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  },
  {
    "puzzleId": "w2",
    "type": "Word-Riddle",
    "prompt": "What has keys but can’t open locks?",
    "answer": "Keyboard",
    "description": "A riddle puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  },
  {
    "puzzleId": "w3",
    "type": "Word-Anagram",
    "prompt": "Unscramble the letters: SILENT",
    "answer": "LISTEN",
    "description": "An anagram puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  }
]
  },
  {
    "userId": "player2",
    "currentPuzzle": 2,
    "totalScore": 80,
    "completedPuzzles": [],
    "toDoPuzzles": [
  {
    "puzzleId": "w1",
    "type": "Word-Cipher",
    "prompt": "Unscramble the letters: CSEAPE",
    "answer": "ESCAPE",
    "description": "A simple word scramble puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  },
  {
    "puzzleId": "w2",
    "type": "Word-Riddle",
    "prompt": "What has keys but can’t open locks?",
    "answer": "Keyboard",
    "description": "A riddle puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  },
  {
    "puzzleId": "w3",
    "type": "Word-Anagram",
    "prompt": "Unscramble the letters: SILENT",
    "answer": "LISTEN",
    "description": "An anagram puzzle.",
    "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
    "isCompleted": false,
    "maxAttempts": 0
  }
]
  }
]
